SAKI BRANSON

Project Manager

From system solutions to promoting Lizzo's newest album, I have produced numerous projects throughout my 5 years of experience. My strengths lie in digital marketing and web production with a background in media design and performing arts.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Production Project Manager

Atlantic Records (Warner Music Group)

OCT 2018 - JUL 2019 // NEW YORK, USA

- Work with designers, digital marketers, and developers to create promotional digital content for all label artists including Bruno Mars, Lizzo, and Ed Sheeran
- Monitor progress of all digital projects via Jira and ensure content adheres to brand/legal guidelines
- Facilitate technical conversations such as hosting, API integrations, and A/B testings with development team and acquire any missing resources
- Collaborate with CRM and E-Commerce teams to improve fan interaction and merchandising sales
- Worked directly with SVP to strategize best practices for the creative team and digital department
- Train junior designers and digital marketers

Creative Project Manager

Worlder Inc.

JUN 2016 - SEP 2018 // NEW YORK, USA

- Liaison between client, internal team, and vendors; overseeing photography, video, web production, and event management projects
- Track progress, scope, and budget of projects and report to client accordingly
- Manage client site content via CMS (Wordpress)
- Supervise and analyze client social accounts
- Assist in web design, animation, and photography creative work

Bid Manager

IBM Japan

APR 2013 - MAR 2015 // TOKYO, JAPAN

- Manage internal teams of engineers and account representatives, and create proposals for clients such as Mizuho Bank and Shiseido
- Compile research data, design pitch decks, and guide projects from brainstorm to final transaction

CONTACT

(347) 963-2877 saki.branson@gmail.com sakibranson.com

SKILLS & TOOLS

- Digital Marketing
- Agile PM Methods
- SEO
- · UX/UI
- · HTML/CSS
- · Adobe Creative Suite
- · Adobe Analytics
- · CMS
- · G Suite
- Google Analytics
- · Microsoft Office
- Jira
- Trello
- Airtable
- Figma

LANGUAGES

- English Native
- · Japanese Native

EDUCATION

The New School

MA in Media Studies

JAN 2016 - MAY 2018 NEW YORK, USA

Focus: Media Design and

Marketing

Waseda University

BA in International Liberal Studies

APR 2009 - MAR 2013 TOKYO, JAPAN

Focus: Media History